# **GIOVANI FRANCISCO**

### ASPIRING SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / BUSINESS IT STUDENT / NURSE

+358 41 318 05 85 giofra.dev@gmail.com Espoo, Finland

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/giovani-francisco/

https://github.com/GeeYouFra

https://geeyoufra.github.io/

#### **PROFILE**



I have the desire and determination to be the best of who I am.

I am a 2nd year IT student honing my skills as a software developer and looking forward to being part of your great company. I am looking for a part-time and work placement as well. If given the opportunity, I would be willing to work and be of value to the company. I would be very pleased to be trained and learn as I see myself diving into an adventure.

Aside from my 8-year involvement in putting smiles on people's lives, I seek to leverage my experience in this new life journey I am taking and am hopeful to be of contribution to your great company.

Filipino English Finnish

#### SKILLS

# **SOFTWARE**

JavaScript HTML/CSS
Java Full Stack
React Node JS

#### PERSONAL OTHERS

Team player PowerBI
Adaptive QlikSense
Self-motivated VS Code
Eager to learn Eclipse

# **EDUCATION**

### HAAGA-HELIA AMK - Pasila Campus

2020 - 2023

Bachelor of Science in Business Information

Technology - BITE

# SATAEDU Satakunnan Koulutuskuntayhtymä

2015 - 2017

Lähihoitaja / Practical Nursing

#### **Benguet State University**

2007 - 2011

Bachelor of Science in Nursing (Philippines)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2015-2017

2013-2014

2012-2013

**Baguio General Hospital** 

**Benguet General Hospital** 

**Koti - Medi**2019-2020

Licensed Practical Nurse
Espoo, Finland

**Terveystalo** Licensed Practical Nurse / Lähihoitaja

2017-2019 Kotihoitotiimi, Hengityshalvauspotilaan hoito

Oulu, Finland

Attendo Oy Licensed Practical Nurse / Lähihoitaja

Kehitysvammaisten hoito

Oulu, Finland

Staff Registered Nurse

Philippines

Staff Registered Nurse

**Philippines**